nlop.com 2006-11-21

# NLOP - Free to Join, No Credit Cards, No Downloads, Real Cash Prizes

**Privacy Policy for Our Players**

**NLOP is absolutely committed to your privacy.**

Your privacy is important to us and we have taken measures to protect the information we collect, as explained below.

What information is collected?  
How will you use my personal information collected online?   
Will NLOP share my personal information with any third parties?  
What is NLOP's complaint policy/procedure?  
Can I opt out of your email list?   
What are cookies used for?  
Do you have an age requirement?  
Do you have data security?  
How do I cancel my membership?  
How do I access or change my personal information?

### What information is collected?

All users are required to register via the online form. We ask that you complete the registration form with accurate information so we can ensure proper prize and award distributions. We ask you to provide the following information; and when you do so, you will be agreeing to the contest terms and conditions. Name  
Address  
Email address  
Birthdate

### How will you use my personal information collected online? 

Without your consent, we will never use your personal information except for the purposes for which it is submitted, such as to register you for participation in a tournament, opt-you in to sponsor offers, reply to your emails, handle your complaints, and process billing and awards payment and business requests related to tournament participation. We may also use such information to provide notifications related to tournament participation. 

Unless you opt out, NLOP from time to time may send you new offers and product promotions to bring selected retail opportunities to our players, and we may include your personal information in a database of names of potential tournament participants provided to organizations running a tournament through NLOP. By responding to such offers and promotions you may be accessing another website. In that case, this Privacy Policy will no longer apply. Instead, you will have to contact those advertisers separately and inform them if you do not wish to receive future mailings from them. And remember, you may opt out of providing your personal information to third party businesses and non-profit organizations by checking the "opt out" box that appears in your game play reminders form us.

### Will NLOP or its partners share my personal information with any third parties? 

**Internal Service Providers.**  
We may use third parties that we refer to as internal service providers to facilitate or outsource one or more aspects of the business, product and service operations that we provide to you on this site (such as search technology and prize distribution) and therefore we may provide some of your personal information directly to these internal service providers. These internal service providers are subject to confidentiality agreements with us and other legal restrictions that prohibit any use of the information we provide them for any purpose other than to facilitate the specific outsourced site-related operation. 

**Legal Requests.**  
We cooperate with law enforcement agencies and will respond to all requests related to a law-enforcement activity by providing the requested information without a subpoena. 

**Our Corporate Family.**  
From time to time we may share your data with our parent, affiliates, subsidiary corporations and entities and joint ventures as well as any other business entity connected with a planned merger with or acquisition by that business entity. Should such a combination occur, we will require that the new combined entity follows this privacy policy with respect to your personal information.(called "Corporate Family") that are committed to serving your online needs and providing related services. To the extent that these entities have access to your information, they will agree to treat it at least as protectively as they treat information they obtain from their other users. Our Corporate Family follows privacy practices substantially similar to NLOP's Privacy Policy. Should any such a combination, merger or acquisition occur, we will require that the new combined entity agrees to follow this Privacy Policy with respect to your personal information.

### What is NLOP's complaint policy/procedure?

In the event a member is not satisfied with any aspect of his/her experience on the NLOP.com site, please contact a Customer Services Representative at: support@pokercreations.com. NLOP.com is committed to resolving any issues quickly and efficiently. 

NLOP.com is continuously monitoring and strengthening its Privacy Commitment. If any changes are made to the Privacy Policy, those changes will be posted here. We recommend that you check frequently for such changes.

### Can I opt out of your email list?

NLOP members are automatically opted-in to receive NLOP emails when you join our service, however, you may opt-out at anytime, and may add or remove your name from any NLOP email list, by sending an email to support@pokercreations.com. 

### What are cookies used for?

NLOP utilizes 'cookies' for convenience so that members will not have to login to the site each time they visit. A cookie is a piece of text that can be entered into the memory of your computer. In this case, it is used to remember your username and password. Most cookies are 'session cookies', meaning that they are automatically deleted at the end of a session. You are always free to decline our cookies, if your browser permits, or ask your browser to indicate when a cookie is being sent. You can also delete cookie files from your computer at your discretion. Note that if you decline our cookies or ask for notification each time a cookie is being sent, you will need to input your username and password each time you visit the NLOP site.

### Do you have an age requirement?

NLOP service is available only to individuals age 18 and older who are United States residents. 

### Do you have data security?

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, NLOP has used appropriate industry-standard procedures to safeguard the confidentially of your personal information, such as firewall, encryption, token authentication, application proxies, monitoring technology, and adaptive analysis of network traffic to track abuse of our network and its data. However, you should assume that no data transmitted over the Internet can be 100% secure. Therefore, although we use industry-standard practices to protect your privacy, we do not promise or guarantee, and you should not expect, that your personal information or private communications will always remain private. When you register to play, NLOP reserves the right to request additional documentation from you to validate prizes or winnings. If you believe that your username or password has been stolen, you are required to notify NLOP so that necessary measures can be taken immediately.

### How do I cancel my membership?

You may cancel your membership at anytime by sending an email to support@pokercreations.com, at which time all previous point earnings are considered forfeited.. If later, you wish to re-enroll, you will be assigned a new account. If you have provided any personal information, you may request that your name be removed from our database at any time. NLOP reserves the right to terminate, cancel or suspend any member's account at anytime without notice. 

### How do I access or change my personal information?

If your personal information changes or you would like to review the personal information we may have on file, please e-mail us with the new information or your review request at support@pokercreations.com. **Once you are logged in, you can access your account iformation by clicking on the My Account tab**.

If you lost your password click on the Lost Pasword button on the home page under the log-in entry bars.

### Exclusions from privacy protection:

The NLOP Privacy Policy does not impose any limits on the collection, use or disclosure of the following information by NLOP: 

a) Information which is available publicly, such as a person's name, address, telephone number and address, when listed in a directory or made available through directory assistance; 

b) Aggregate information that cannot be associated with a specific person, such as demographic statistics about NLOP's customers or players, or number of visitors and average time spent on a website.
